[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Where does Ms. Candrell go on summer vacation in the movie Dont Tell Mom the Babysitters Dead?", "correct_answer": "Australia", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "Florida", "Antarctica"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This earthquake occurred on August 17, 1999, and had a magnitude of 7.4. The reported number of casualties was approximately 17,000. Where did this disaster take place?", "correct_answer": "Turkey", "incorrect_answers": ["China", "Spain", "The United States"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Los Angeles Earthquake of 1916 caused a 3-day fire.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "From what 1931 horror movie is the popular line Its alive! Its alive!?", "correct_answer": "Frankenstein", "incorrect_answers": ["Childs Play", "Dracula", "The Thing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the mall where Marty and Doc meet at the beginning of the movie Back to the Future?", "correct_answer": "Twin Pines Mall", "incorrect_answers": ["Lone Pine Mall", "Pine Mall", "Hill Valley Pine Mall"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 1997 drama, directed by Jack Bender, focuses on the problems of Suzanne Boxer, an unstable young girl who befriends Heather, as she dreams of having Heathers life.", "correct_answer": "Friends Til the End", "incorrect_answers": ["A Friendship To Die For", "A Friend of the Family", "A Girl Thing"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What father-daughter film stars as on-screen father and daughter Moses and Addie in the movie Paper Moon?", "correct_answer": "Ryan ONeal and Tatum ONeal", "incorrect_answers": ["None of these", "Paul Newman and Nell Potts", "Henry Fonda and Jane Fonda"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these stories was written by the Brothers Grimm?", "correct_answer": "The Frog Prince", "incorrect_answers": ["The Adventures of Pinocchio", "Puss in Boots", "Sleeping Beauty"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is Han Solos partner in smuggling in the Star Wars saga?", "correct_answer": "Chewbacca", "incorrect_answers": ["Greedo", "Boba Fett", "Jabba the Hutt"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who is the hapless kitty villain who is constantly being outwitted by the little bird Tweety Pie?", "correct_answer": "Sylvester", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom", "Wil E. Cat", "Garfield"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which 1996 animated live-action film featured cartoon character Marvin the Martian?", "correct_answer": "Space Jam", "incorrect_answers": ["Toy Story", "Spiderman", "Robots"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The winner  of the 27th Razzie for Worse Director for his film Lady in the Water used to be a darling of the film critics. What director should be saying I see dead box office.?", "correct_answer": "M. Night Shyamalan", "incorrect_answers": ["David Lynch", "Tim Burton", "Ron Howard"]}]